THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- CJP Phase I, 1990-2004; 1; 30.4
  - Audiotapes of Juror Interviews, 1990-2004; 1.3
    - NC 1153, Undated (Cassette 1246)
    - NC 1154, Undated (Cassette 1247)
    - NC 1154, Undated (Cassette 1248)
    - NC 1155, Undated (Cassette 1249)
    - NC 1155, Undated (Cassette 1250)
    - NC 1155, Undated (Cassette 1251)
    - NC 1155, Undated (Cassette 1252)
    - PA 0944, Undated (Cassette 1253)
    - PA 0944, Undated (Cassette 1254)
    - PA 0944, Undated (Cassette 1255)
    - PA 0945, Undated (Cassette 1256)
    - PA 0946, Undated (Cassette 1257)
    - PA 0946, Undated (Cassette 1258)
    - PA 0947, Undated (Cassette 1259)
    - PA 0947, Undated (Cassette 1260)
    - PA 0947, Undated (Cassette 1261)
    - PA 0948, Undated (Cassette 1262)
    - PA 0948, Undated (Cassette 1263)
    - PA 0948, Undated (Cassette 1264)
    - PA 0949, Undated (Cassette 1265)
    - PA 0949, Undated (Cassette 1266)
    - PA 0950, Undated (Cassette 1267)
    - PA 0950, Undated (Cassette 1268)
    - PA 0950, Undated (Cassette 1269)
    - PA 0951, Undated (Cassette 1270)
    - PA 0951, Undated (Cassette 1271)
    - PA 0952, Undated (Cassette 1272)
    - PA 0952, Undated (Cassette 1273)
    - PA 0953, Undated (Cassette 1274)
    - PA 0953, Undated (Cassette 1275)
    - PA 0953, Undated (Cassette 1276)
    - PA 0954, Undated (Cassette 1277)
    - PA 0954, Undated (Cassette 1278)
    - PA 0954, Undated (Cassette 1279)
    - PA 0954, Undated (Cassette 1280)
    - PA0954, Undated (Cassette 1281)
    - PA 0955, Undated (Cassette 1282)
    - PA 0955, Undated (Cassette 1283)
    - PA 0956, Undated (Cassette 1284)
    - PA 0956, Undated (Cassette 1285)
    - PA 0957, Undated (Cassette 1286)
    - PA 0957, Undated (Cassette 1287)
    - PA 0957, Undated (Cassette 1288)
    - PA 0980, Undated (Cassette 1289)
    - PA 0980, Undated (Cassette 1290)
    - PA 0980, Undated (Cassette 1291)
    - PA 0981, Undated (Cassette 1292)
    - PA 0981, Undated (Cassette 1293)
    - PA 0981, Undated (Cassette 1294)
    - PA 0982, Undated (Cassette 1295)
    - PA 0982, Undated (Cassette 1296)
    - PA 0983, Undated (Cassette 1297)
    - PA 0983, Undated (Cassette 1298)
    - PA 0985, Undated (Cassette 1299)
    - PA 0985/ PA 0986, Undated (Cassette 1300)
    - PA 4001, Undated (Cassette 1301)
    - PA 4005, Undated (Mini-dv 1302)
    - PA 4005, Undated (Mini-dv 1303)
    - PA, Undated (Cassette 1304)
    - PA, Undated (Cassette 1305)
    - PA, Undated (Cassette 1306)
    - SC 1203, Undated (Cassette 1307)
    - SC 1203, Undated (Cassette 1308)
    - SC 1204, Undated (Cassette 1309)
    - SC 1204, Undated (Cassette 1310)
    - SC 1205, Undated (Cassette 1311)
    - SC 1205, Undated (Cassette 1312)
    - SC 1206, Undated (Cassette 1313)
    - SC 1206, Undated (Cassette 1314)
    - SC 1206, Undated (Cassette 1315)
    - SC 1207, Undated (Cassette 1316)
    - SC 1207, Undated (Cassette 1317)
    - SC 1207, Undated (Cassette 1318)
    - SC 1207, Undated (Cassette 1319)
    - SC 1208, Undated (Cassette 1320)
    - SC 1208, Undated (Cassette 1321)
    - SC 1208, Undated (Cassette 1322)
    - SC 1210, Undated (Cassette 1323)
    - SC 1210, Undated (Cassette 1324)
    - SC 1211, Undated (Cassette 1325)
    - SC 1211, Undated (Cassette 1326)
    - SC 1212, Undated (Cassette 1327)
    - SC 1213, Undated (Cassette 1328)
    - SC 1213, Undated (Cassette 1329)
    - SC 1213, Undated (Cassette 1330)
    - SC 1214, Undated (Cassette 1331)
    - SC 1214, Undated (Cassette 1332)
    - SC 1214, Undated (Cassette 1333)
    - SC 1215, Undated (Cassette 1334)
    - SC 1215, Undated (Cassette 1335)
    - SC 1215, Undated (Cassette 1336)
    - SC 1216, Undated (Cassette 1337)
    - SC 1216, Undated (Cassette 1338)
    - SC 1217, Undated (Cassette 1339)
    - SC 1217, Undated (Cassette 1340)
    - SC 1217, Undated (Cassette 1341)
    - SC 1218, Undated (Cassette 1342)
    - SC 1218, Undated (Cassette 1343)
    - SC 1218, Undated (Cassette 1344)
    - SC 1218, Undated (Cassette 1345)
    - SC 1219, Undated (Cassette 1346)
    - SC 1219, Undated (Cassette 1347)
    - SC 1220, Undated (Cassette 1348)
    - SC 1220, Undated (Cassette 1349)
    - SC 1221, Undated (Cassette 1350)
    - SC 1221, Undated (Cassette 1351)
    - SC 1221, Undated (Cassette 1352)
    - SC 1221, Undated (Cassette 1353)
    - SC 1222, Undated (Cassette 1354)
    - SC 1222, Undated (Cassette 1355)
    - SC 1223, Undated (Cassette 1356)
    - SC 1223, Undated (Cassette 1357)
    - SC 1224, Undated (Cassette 1358)
    - SC 1224, Undated (Cassette 1359)
    - SC 1224, Undated (Cassette 1360)
    - SC 1224, Undated (Cassette 1361)
    - SC 1225, Undated (Cassette 1362)
    - SC 1225, Undated (Cassette 1363)
    - SC 1226, Undated (Cassette 1364)
    - SC 1226, Undated (Cassette 1365)
    - SC 1227, Undated (Cassette 1366)
    - SC 1227, Undated (Cassette 1367)
    - SC 1228, Undated (Cassette 1368)
    - SC 1228, Undated (Cassette 1369)
    - SC 1229, Undated (Cassette 1370)
    - SC 1229, Undated (Cassette 1371)
    - SC 1229, Undated (Cassette 1372)
    - SC 1230, Undated (Cassette 1373)
    - SC 1230, Undated (Cassette 1374)
    - SC 1231, Undated (Cassette 1375)
    - SC 1231, Undated (Cassette 1376)
    - SC 1232, Undated (Cassette 1377)
    - SC 1232, Undated (Cassette 1378)
    - SC 1232, Undated (Cassette 1379)
    - SC 1233, Undated (Cassette 1380)
    - SC 1233, Undated (Cassette 1381)
    - SC 1233, Undated (Cassette 1382)
    - SC 1234, Undated (Cassette 1383)
    - SC 1234, Undated (Cassette 1384)
    - SC 1234, Undated (Cassette 1385)
    - SC 1235, Undated (Cassette 1386)
    - SC 1235, Undated (Cassette 1387)
    - SC 1236, Undated (Cassette 1388)
    - SC 1236, Undated (Cassette 1389)
    - SC 1237, Undated (Cassette 1390)
    - SC 1237, Undated (Cassette 1391)
    - SC 1239, Undated (Cassette 1392)
    - SC 1239, Undated (Cassette 1393)
    - SC 1239, Undated (Cassette 1394)
    - SC 1241, Undated (Cassette 1395)
    - SC 1241, Undated (Cassette 1396)
    - SC 1243, Undated (Cassette 1397)
    - SC 1243, Undated (Cassette 1398)
    - SC 1243, Undated (Cassette 1399)
    - SC 1244, Undated (Cassette 1400)
    - SC 1244, Undated (Cassette 1401)
    - SC 1245, Undated (Cassette 1402)
    - SC 1245, Undated (Cassette 1403)
    - SC 1245, Undated (Cassette 1404)
    - SC 1246, Undated (Cassette 1405)
    - SC 1247, Undated (Cassette 1406)
    - SC 1247, Undated (Cassette 1407)
    - SC 1247, Undated (Cassette 1408)
    - SC 1248, Undated (Cassette 1409)
    - SC 1248, Undated (Cassette 1410)
    - SC 1249, Undated (Cassette 1411)
    - SC 1249, Undated (Cassette 1412)
    - SC 1250, Undated (Cassette 1413)
    - SC 1250, Undated (Cassette 1414)
    - SC 1250, Undated (Cassette 1415)
    - SC 1250, Undated (Cassette 1416)
    - SC 1251, Undated (Cassette 1417)
    - SC 1251, Undated (Cassette 1418)
    - SC 1251, Undated (Cassette 1419)
    - SC 1252, Undated (Cassette 1420)
    - SC 1252, Undated (Cassette 1421)
    - SC 1253, Undated (Cassette 1422)
    - SC 1254, Undated (Cassette 1423)
    - SC 1255, Undated (Cassette 1424)
    - SC 1256, Undated (Cassette 1425)
    - SC 1257, Undated (Cassette 1426)
    - SC 1257, Undated (Cassette 1427)
    - SC 1258, Undated (Cassette 1428)
    - SC 1258, Undated (Cassette 1429)
    - SC 1258, Undated (Cassette 1430)
    - SC 1259, Undated (Cassette 1431)
    - SC 1260, Undated (Cassette 1432)
    - SC 1260, Undated (Cassette 1433)
    - SC 1260, Undated (Cassette 1434)
    - SC 1261, Undated (Cassette 1435)
    - SC 1261, Undated (Cassette 1436)
    - SC 1261, Undated (Cassette 1437)
    - SC 1262, Undated (Cassette 1438)
    - SC 1262, Undated (Cassette 1439)
    - SC 1262, Undated (Cassette 1440)
    - SC 1263, Undated (Cassette 1441)
    - SC 1263, Undated (Cassette 1442)
    - SC 1264, Undated (Cassette 1443)
    - SC 1264, Undated (Cassette 1444)
    - SC 1265, Undated (Cassette 1445)
    - SC 1265, Undated (Cassette 1446)
    - SC 1267, Undated (Cassette 1447)
    - SC 1267, Undated (Cassette 1448)
    - SC 1267, Undated (Cassette 1449)
    - SC 1268, Undated (Cassette 1450)
    - SC 1268, Undated (Cassette 1451)
    - SC 1270, Undated (Cassette 1452)
    - SC 1270, Undated (Cassette 1453)
    - SC 1271, Undated (Cassette 1454)
    - SC 1271, Undated (Cassette 1455)
    - SC 1272, Undated (Cassette 1456)
    - SC 1272, Undated (Cassette 1457)
    - SC 1274, Undated (Cassette 1458)
    - SC 1274, Undated (Cassette 1459)
    - SC 1276, Undated (Cassette 1460)
    - SC 1276, Undated (Cassette 1461)
    - SC 1278, Undated (Cassette 1462)
    - SC 1278, Undated (Cassette 1463)
    - SC 1282, Undated (Cassette 1464)
    - SC 1282, Undated (Cassette 1465)
    - SC 1282, Undated (Cassette 1466)
    - SC 1282, Undated (Cassette 1467)
    - SC 1282, Undated (Cassette 1468)
    - SC 1286, Undated (Cassette 1469)
    - SC 1286, Undated (Cassette 1470)
    - SC 1287, Undated (Cassette 1471)
    - SC 1287, Undated (Cassette 1472)
    - SC 1287, Undated (Cassette 1473)
    - SC 1288, Undated (Cassette 1474)
    - SC 1288, Undated (Cassette 1475)
    - SC 1289, Undated (Cassette 1476)
    - SC 1289, Undated (Cassette 1477)
    - SC 1290, Undated (Cassette 1478)
    - SC 1291, Undated (Cassette 1479)
    - SC 1292, Undated (Cassette 1480)
    - SC 1292, Undated (Cassette 1481)
    - SC 1292, Undated (Cassette 1482)
    - SC 1292, Undated (Cassette 1483)
    - SC 1292, Undated (Cassette 1484)
    - SC 1293, Undated (Cassette 1485)
    - SC 1293, Undated (Cassette 1486)
    - SC 1294, Undated (Cassette 1487)
    - SC 1294, Undated (Cassette 1488)
    - SC 1295, Undated (Cassette 1489)
    - SC 1296, Undated (Cassette 1490)
    - SC 1296, Undated (Cassette 1491)
    - SC 1298, Undated (Cassette 1492)
    - SC 1298, Undated (Cassette 1493)
    - SC 1302, Undated (Cassette 1494)
    - SC 1302, Undated (Cassette 1495)
    - SC 1302, Undated (Cassette 1496)
    - SC 1304, Undated (Cassette 1497)
    - SC 1304, Undated (Cassette 1498)
    - SC 1305, Undated (Cassette 1499)
    - SC 1305, Undated (Cassette 1500)
    - SC 1306, Undated (Cassette 1501)
    - SC 1306, Undated (Cassette 1502)
    - SC 1306, Undated (Cassette 1503)
    - SC 1307, Undated (Cassette 1504)
    - SC 1308, Undated (Cassette 1505)
    - SC 1308, Undated (Cassette 1506)
    - SC 1308, Undated (Cassette 1507)
    - SC 1309, Undated (Cassette 1508)
    - SC 1309, Undated (Cassette 1509)
    - SC 1310, Undated (Cassette 1510)
    - SC 1310, Undated (Cassette 1511)
    - SC 1310, Undated (Cassette 1512)
    - SC 1310, Undated (Cassette 1513)
    - SC 1311, Undated (Cassette 1514)
    - SC 1311, Undated (Cassette 1515)
    - SC 1312, Undated (Cassette 1516)
    - SC 1312, Undated (Cassette 1517)
    - SC 1312, Undated (Cassette 1518)
    - SC 1313, Undated (Cassette 1519)
    - SC 1313, Undated (Cassette 1520)
    - SC 1314, Undated (Cassette 1521)
    - SC 1314, Undated (Cassette 1522)
    - SC 1315, Undated (Cassette 1523)
    - SC 1315, Undated (Cassette 1524)
    - SC 1316, Undated (Cassette 1525)
    - SC 1316, Undated (Cassette 1526)
    - SC 1317, Undated (Cassette 1527)
    - SC 1317, Undated (Cassette 1528)
    - SC 1318, Undated (Cassette 1529)
    - SC 1318, Undated (Cassette 1530)
    - SC 1319, Undated (Cassette 1531)
    - SC 1319, Undated (Cassette 1532)
    - SC 1320, Undated (Cassette 1533)
    - SC 1320, Undated (Cassette 1534)
    - SC 1321, Undated (Cassette 1535)
    - SC 1321, Undated (Cassette 1536)
    - SC 1322, Undated (Cassette 1537)
    - SC 1323, Undated (Cassette 1538)
    - SC 1324, Undated (Cassette 1539)
    - SC 1324, Undated (Cassette 1540)
    - SC 1325, Undated (Cassette 1541)
    - SC 1325, Undated (Cassette 1542)
    - TN 2001, Undated (Cassette 1543)
    - TN 2001, Undated (Cassette 1544)
    - TN 2001, Undated (Cassette 1545)
    - TN 2002, Undated (Cassette 1546)
    - TN 2002, Undated (Cassette 1547)
    - TN 2002, Undated (Cassette 1548)
    - TN 2003, Undated (Cassette 1549)
    - TN 2003, Undated (Cassette 1550)
    - TN 2003, Undated (Cassette 1551)
    - TN 2003, Undated (Cassette 1552)
    - TN 2003, Undated (Cassette 1553)
    - TN 2004, Undated (Cassette 1554)
    - TN 2004, Undated (Cassette 1555)
    - TN 2004, Undated (Cassette 1556)
    - TN 2004, Undated (Cassette 1557)
    - TN 2005, Undated (Cassette 1558)
    - TN 2005, Undated (Cassette 1559)
    - TN 2005, Undated (Cassette 1560)
    - TN 2006, Undated (Cassette 1561)
    - TN 2006, Undated (Cassette 1562)
    - TN 2006, Undated (Cassette 1563)
    - TN 2009, Undated (Cassette 1564)
    - TN 2009, Undated (Cassette 1565)
    - TN 2010, Undated (Cassette 1566)
    - TN 2010, Undated (Cassette 1567)
    - TN 2010, Undated (Cassette 1568)
    - TN 2011, Undated (Cassette 1569)
    - TN 2011, Undated (Cassette 1570)
    - TN 2012, Undated (Cassette 1571)
    - TN 2012, Undated (Cassette 1572)
    - TN 2012, Undated (Cassette 1573)
    - TN 2012, Undated (Cassette 1574)
    - TN 2012, Undated (Cassette 1575)
    - TN 2013, Undated (Cassette 1576)
    - TN 2013, Undated (Cassette 1577)
    - TN 2013, Undated (Cassette 1578)
    - TN 2013, Undated (Cassette 1579)
    - TN 2014, Undated (Cassette 1580)
    - TN 2014, Undated (Cassette 1581)
    - TN 2014, Undated (Cassette 1582)
    - TN 2015, Undated (Cassette 1583)
    - TN 2015, Undated (Cassette 1584)
    - TN 2015, Undated (Cassette 1585)
    - TN 2015, Undated (Cassette 1586)
    - TN 2016, Undated (Cassette 1587)
    - TN 2016, Undated (Cassette 1588)
    - TN 2016, Undated (Cassette 1589)
    - TN 2017, Undated (Cassette 1590)
    - TN 2017, Undated (Cassette 1591)
    - TN 2017, Undated (Cassette 1592)
    - TN 2017, Undated (Cassette 1593)
    - TN 2018, Undated (Cassette 1594)
    - TN 2018, Undated (Cassette 1595)
    - TN 2018, Undated (Cassette 1596)
    - TN 2018, Undated (Cassette 1597)
    - TN 2023, Undated (Cassette 1598)
    - TN 2024, Undated (Cassette 1599)
    - TN 2024, Undated (Cassette 1600)
    - TN 2024, Undated (Cassette 1601)
    - TN 2025, Undated (Cassette 1602)
    - TN 2025, Undated (Cassette 1603)
    - TN 2025, Undated (Cassette 1604)
    - TN 2026, Undated (Cassette 1605)
    - TN 2027, Undated (Cassette 1606)
    - TN 2027, Undated (Cassette 1607)
    - TN 2027, Undated (Cassette 1608)
    - TN 2028, Undated (Cassette 1609)
    - TN 2028, Undated (Cassette 1610)
    - TN 2029, Undated (Cassette 1611)
    - TN 2029, Undated (Cassette 1612)
    - TN 2029, Undated (Cassette 1613)
    - TN 2029, Undated (Cassette 1614)
    - TN 2030, Undated (Cassette 1615)
    - TN 2030, Undated (Cassette 1616)
    - TN 2030, Undated (Cassette 1617)
    - TN 2034, Undated (Cassette 1618)
    - TN 2034, Undated (Cassette 1619)
    - TN 2035, Undated (Cassette 1620)
    - TN 2035, Undated (Cassette 1621)
    - TN 2036, Undated (Cassette 1622)
    - TN 2036, Undated (Cassette 1623)
    - TN 2037, Undated (Cassette 1624)
    - TN 2037, Undated (Cassette 1625)
    - TN 2038, Undated (Cassette 1626)
    - TN 2038, Undated (Cassette 1627)
    - TN 2038, Undated (Cassette 1628)
    - TN 2039, Undated (Cassette 1629)
    - TN 2039, Undated (Cassette 1630)
    - TN 2040, Undated (Mini-dv 1631)
    - TN 2040, Undated (Mini-dv 1632)
    - TN 2041, Undated (Mini-dv 1633)
    - TN 2041, Undated (Mini-dv 1634)
    - TN 2042, Undated (Mini-dv 1635)
    - TN 2042, Undated (Mini-dv 1636)
    - TN 2043, Undated (Mini-dv 1637)
    - TN 2044, Undated (Mini-dv 1638)
    - TN 2044, Undated (Cassette 1639)
    - TN 2045, Undated (Mini-dv 1640)
    - TN 2045, Undated (Mini-dv 1641)
    - TN 2046, Undated (Cassette 1642)
    - TN 2046, Undated (Cassette 1643)
    - TN 2046, Undated (Mini-dv 1644)
    - TN 2047, Undated (Cassette 1645)
    - TN 2047, Undated (Cassette 1646)
    - TN 2048, Undated (Cassette 1647)
    - TN 2048, Undated (Cassette 1648)
    - TN 2049, Undated (Cassette 1649)
    - TN 2049, Undated (Cassette 1650)
    - TN 2050, Undated (Cassette 1651)
    - TN 2050, Undated (Cassette 1652)
    - TN 2051, Undated (Mini-dv 1653)
    - TX 1573, Undated (Cassette 1654)
    - TX 1573, Undated (Cassette 1655)
    - TX 1573, Undated (Cassette 1656)
    - TX 1574, Undated (Cassette 1657)
    - TX 1574, Undated (Cassette 1658)
    - TX 1574, Undated (Cassette 1659)
    - TX 1575, Undated (Cassette 1660)
    - TX 1575, Undated (Cassette 1661)
    - TX 1575, Undated (Cassette 1662)
    - TX 1576, Undated (Cassette 1663)
    - TX 1576, Undated (Cassette 1664)
    - TX 1577, Undated (Cassette 1665)
    - TX 1577, Undated (Cassette 1666)
    - TX 1578, Undated (Cassette 1667)
    - TX 1578, Undated (Cassette 1668)
    - TX 1578, Undated (Cassette 1669)
    - TX 1579, Undated (Cassette 1670)
    - TX 1579, Undated (Cassette 1671)
    - TX 1579, Undated (Cassette 1672)
    - TX 1579, Undated (Cassette 1673)
    - TX 1580, Undated (Cassette 1674)
    - TX 1580, Undated (Cassette 1675)
    - TX 1580, Undated (Cassette 1676)
    - TX 1581, Undated (Cassette 1677)
    - TX 1581, Undated (Cassette 1678)
    - TX 1582, Undated (Cassette 1679)
    - TX 1582, Undated (Cassette 1680)
    - TX 1583, Undated (Cassette 1681)
    - TX 1583, Undated (Cassette 1682)
    - TX 1583, Undated (Cassette 1683)
    - TX 1584, Undated (Cassette 1684)
    - TX 1584, Undated (Cassette 1685)
    - TX 1584, Undated (Cassette 1686)
    - TX 1585, Undated (Cassette 1687)
    - TX 1585, Undated (Cassette 1688)
    - TX 1585, Undated (Cassette 1689)
    - TX 1586, Undated (Cassette 1690)
    - TX 1586, Undated (Cassette 1691)
    - TX 1586, Undated (Cassette 1692)
    - TX 1587, Undated (Cassette 1693)
    - TX 1587, Undated (Cassette 1694)
    - TX 1587, Undated (Cassette 1695)
    - TX 1587, Undated (Cassette 1696)
    - TX 1588, Undated (Cassette 1697)
    - TX 1588, Undated (Cassette 1698)
    - TX 1588, Undated (Cassette 1699)
    - TX 1589, Undated (Cassette 1700)
    - TX 1589, Undated (Cassette 1701)
    - TX 1590, Undated (Cassette 1702)
    - TX 1590, Undated (Cassette 1703)
    - TX 1590, Undated (Cassette 1704)
    - TX 1591, Undated (Cassette 1705)
    - TX 1591, Undated (Cassette 1706)
    - TX 1592, Undated (Cassette 1707)
    - TX 1593, Undated (Cassette 1708)
    - TX 1593, Undated (Cassette 1709)
    - TX 1593, Undated (Cassette 1710)
    - TX 1596, Undated (Cassette 1711)
    - TX 1596, Undated (Cassette 1712)
    - TX 1596, Undated (Cassette 1713)
    - TX 1597, Undated (Cassette 1714)
    - TX 1597, Undated (Cassette 1715)
    - TX 1597, Undated (Cassette 1716)
    - TX 1598, Undated (Cassette 1717)
    - TX 1598, Undated (Cassette 1718)
    - TX 1598, Undated (Cassette 1719)
    - TX 1598, Undated (Cassette 1720)
    - TX 1599, Undated (Cassette 1721)
    - TX 1599, Undated (Cassette 1722)
    - TX 1600, Undated (Cassette 1723)
    - TX 1600, Undated (Cassette 1724)
    - TX 1600, Undated (Cassette 1725)
    - TX 1600, Undated (Cassette 1726)
    - TX 1601, Undated (Cassette 1727)
    - TX 1601, Undated (Cassette 1728)
    - TX 1602, Undated (Cassette 1729)
    - TX 1602, Undated (Cassette 1730)
    - TX 1605, Undated (Cassette 1731)
    - TX 1605, Undated (Cassette 1732)
    - TX 1606, Undated (Cassette 1733)
    - TX 1606, Undated (Cassette 1734)
    - TX 1606, Undated (Cassette 1735)
    - TX 1607, Undated (Cassette 1736)
    - TX 1607, Undated (Cassette 1737)
    - TX 1608, Undated (Cassette 1738)
    - TX 1608, Undated (Cassette 1739)
    - TX 1609, Undated (Cassette 1740)
    - TX 1609, Undated (Cassette 1741)
    - TX 1609, Undated (Cassette 1742)
    - TX 1610, Undated (Cassette 1743)
    - TX 1610, Undated (Cassette 1744)
    - TX 1611, Undated (Cassette 1745)
    - TX 1611, Undated (Cassette 1746)
    - TX 1611, Undated (Cassette 1747)
    - TX 1612, Undated (Cassette 1748)
    - TX 1612, Undated (Cassette 1749)
    - TX 1612, Undated (Cassette 1750)
    - TX 1613, Undated (Cassette 1751)
    - TX 1613, Undated (Cassette 1752)
    - TX 1613, Undated (Cassette 1753)
    - TX 1614, Undated (Cassette 1754)
    - TX 1614, Undated (Cassette 1755)
    - TX 1614, Undated (Cassette 1756)
    - TX 1614, Undated (Cassette 1757)
    - TX 1615, Undated (Cassette 1758)
    - TX 1615, Undated (Cassette 1759)
    - TX 1615, Undated (Cassette 1760)
    - TX 1616, Undated (Cassette 1761)
    - TX 1616, Undated (Cassette 1762)
    - TX 1616, Undated (Cassette 1763)
    - TX 1617, Undated (Cassette 1764)
    - TX 1617, Undated (Cassette 1765)
    - TX 1617, Undated (Cassette 1766)
    - TX 1618, Undated (Cassette 1767)
    - TX 1618, Undated (Cassette 1768)
    - TX 1618, Undated (Cassette 1769)
    - TX 1619, Undated (Cassette 1770)
    - TX 1619, Undated (Cassette 1771)
    - TX 1620, Undated (Cassette 1772)
    - TX 1620, Undated (Cassette 1773)
    - TX 1620, Undated (Cassette 1774)
    - TX 1621, Undated (Cassette 1775)
    - TX 1621, Undated (Cassette 1776)
    - TX 1646, Undated (Cassette 1777)
    - TX 1646, Undated (Cassette 1778)
    - TX 1646, Undated (Cassette 1779)
    - TX 1647, Undated (Cassette 1780)
    - TX 1647, Undated (Cassette 1781)
    - TX 1648, Undated (Cassette 1782)
    - TX 1648, Undated (Cassette 1783)
    - TX 1648, Undated (Cassette 1784)
    - TX 1649, Undated (Cassette 1785)
    - TX 1649, Undated (Cassette 1786)
    - TX 1650, Undated (Cassette 1787)
    - TX 1650, Undated (Cassette 1788)
    - TX 5000, Undated (Cassette 1789)
    - TX 5000, Undated (Cassette 1790)
    - TX 5000, Undated (Cassette 1791)
    - TX 5001, Undated (Cassette 1792)
    - TX 5001, Undated (Cassette 1793)
    - TX 5001, Undated (Cassette 1794)
    - TX 5001, Undated (Cassette 1795)
    - TX 5002, Undated (Cassette 1796)
    - TX 5002, Undated (Cassette 1797)
    - TX 5002, Undated (Cassette 1798)
    - TX 5003, Undated (Cassette 1799)
    - TX 5003, Undated (Cassette 1800)
    - TX 5003, Undated (Cassette 1801)
    - TX 5003, Undated (Cassette 1802)
    - TX 5004, Undated (Cassette 1803)
    - TX 5004, Undated (Cassette 1804)
    - TX 5004, Undated (Cassette 1805)
    - TX 5005, Undated (Cassette 1806)
    - TX 5005, Undated (Cassette 1807)
    - TX 5006, Undated (Cassette 1808)
    - TX 5006, Undated (Cassette 1809)
    - TX 5007, Undated (Cassette 1810)
    - TX 5007, Undated (Cassette 1811)
    - TX 5007, Undated (Cassette 1812)
    - TX 5008, Undated (Cassette 1813)
    - TX 5008, Undated (Cassette 1814)
    - TX 5009, Undated (Cassette 1815)
    - TX 5010, Undated (Cassette 1816)
    - TX 5010, Undated (Cassette 1817)
    - TX 5016, Undated (Cassette 1818)
    - TX 5016, Undated (Cassette 1819)
    - TX, Undated (Cassette 1820)
    - TX, Undated (Cassette 1821)
    - TX, Undated (Cassette 1822)
    - TX, Undated (Cassette 1823)
    - TX, Undated (Cassette 1824)
    - VA 1651, Undated (Cassette 1825)
    - VA 1651, Undated (Cassette 1826)
    - VA 1653, Undated (Cassette 1827)
    - VA 1653, Undated (Cassette 1828)
    - VA 1655, Undated (Cassette 1829)
    - VA 1655, Undated (Cassette 1830)
    - VA 1657, Undated (Cassette 1831)
    - VA 1657, Undated (Cassette 1832)
    - VA 1658, Undated (Cassette 1833)
    - VA 1658, Undated (Cassette 1834)
    - VA 1658, Undated (Cassette 1835)
    - VA 1660, Undated (Cassette 1836)
    - VA 1660, Undated (Cassette 1837)
    - VA 1661, Undated (Cassette 1838)
    - VA 1661, Undated (Cassette 1839)
    - VA 1662, Undated (Cassette 1840)
    - VA 1662, Undated (Cassette 1841)
    - VA 1663, Undated (Cassette 1842)
    - VA 1664, Undated (Cassette 1843)
    - VA 1665, Undated (Cassette 1844)
    - VA 1665, Undated (Cassette 1845)
    - VA 1665, Undated (Cassette 1846)
    - VA 1666, Undated (Cassette 1847)
    - VA 1666, Undated (Cassette 1848)
    - VA 1667, Undated (Cassette 1849)
    - VA 1667, Undated (Cassette 1850)
    - VA 1667, Undated (Cassette 1851)
    - VA 1668, Undated (Cassette 1852)
    - VA 1668, Undated (Cassette 1853)
    - VA 1669, Undated (Cassette 1854)
    - VA 1670, Undated (Cassette 1855)
    - VA 1670, Undated (Cassette 1856)